<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vidyotan2</string>
    <string name="left_image" />
    <string name="college_name" >Sipna College of Engineering \n and Technology, Amravati</string>
    <string name="right_image" />
    <string name="background_image">Background Image</string>
    <string name="overlay_image">Overlay Image</string>
    <string name="_2024">2024</string>
    <string name="Slogan">A National level Techfest where Imagination meets Innovation</string>
    <string name="about_vidyotan">ABOUT VIDYOTAN</string>
    <string name="info">Vidyotan" is the annual Science and Technology based National level activity of Sipna College of Engineering and Technology, Amravati. The sole purpose of organizing this techfest  event is to give the students a platform to complete from all around to showcase their talent and skills in various integrated techno events. These events promote a real technical trade for the budding engineers to come up with their bright ideas.</string>
    <string name="info2">This year the Vidyotan theme is Chadryayan-3 Exploring The Universe.</string>
    <string name="info3">It Is organized on the 8th feb 2024</string>
    <string name="event">EVENTS IN VIDYOTAN</string>
    <string name="sc">Startup Conclave</string>
    <string name="btn1">Event Details</string>
    <string name="tc">Technical Quiz</string>
    <string name="csl">Civil Snake Ladder</string>
    <string name="bc">Box Cricket</string>
    <string name="cf">Circuit Fixer</string>
    <string name="dyts">Design yout T-Shirt</string>
    <string name="wa">Web/App Design</string>
    <string name="dth">Digital Treasure Hunt</string>
    <string name="ipl">IPL Auction</string>
    <string name="pc">Paper Castle</string>
    <string name="es">E-Sport</string>
    <string name="ss">Shutter Splash</string>
    <string name="robo">Robotics</string>
    <string name="mat">Make-A-Thon</string>
    <string name="sds">Screen D Structure</string>
    <string name="spazio">Spazio</string>
    <string name="yp">Yaksha Prashna</string>
    <string name="ps">Photo gallery</string>
    <string name="event_name_startup_conclave">Event Name: Startup Conclave</string>
    <string name="intro">Embark on a transformative journey at our Startup Conclave where diverse teams showcase unique ideas, pitch to judges and compete for prizes, fostering innovation and entrepreneurial excellence</string>
    <string name="date_and_time_8th_february_2024">Date and Time: 8th February 2024</string>
    <string name="location">Location : Sipna College of Engineering and Technology,Amravati</string>
    <string name="entry_fees">Entry Fees:\n • One/Two Partcipants: 200/- \n • Tree/Four Participants: 300/-</string>
    <string name="prize">Prizes:\n • Winner: ₹5000 \n •Runner Up: ₹3000</string>
    <string name="coordinator">Coordinators: \n1) Shreejit Umale: 9359583740\n2) Shruti Khandare: 9146342158\n3) Gauri Deshmukh : 8975531687\n4) Chanchal Rathi :8767227496</string>
    <string name="rules_amp_rugulations"><![CDATA[Rules & Rugulations]]></string>
    <string name="rules">1. A team must consist of a maximum of 4 and a minimum of 1 participant.\n2. Each team is allowed to present only one startup idea.\n 3. Team members can be from the same or different fields and colleges.\n 4. Internet facilities will not be provided during the event.\n 5. No mentors will be provided by the organizing committee.\n 6. Participants must report at 9 am on the event day.\n 7. Participants are required to bring their own laptop or pen drive containing their presentations or any necessary hard copies.\n 8. Pitching will be conducted individually in front of the judges.\n 9. Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day.\n 10. All the participants will be awarded with  Participation Certificates .</string>
    <string name="note">Note: No abusive language, unfair mean will be tolerated, In such case the team will be disqualified.</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="event_name_tecnical_quiz">Event Name: Tecnical Quiz</string>
    <string name="circuit_prize">Prizes:\n Group A:              Group B:\n Winner: &#8377;3000         Winner: &#8377;3000\n Runner Up: &#8377;2000        Runner Up: &#8377;2000</string>
    <string name="tecnical_quiz"><b>Round 1: Basic Engineering Technical GK\n </b>1) Number of questions - 50\n 2) Time to solve - 20 mins\n 3) Topics-Basic engineering, General science, etc\n 4) No negative marking.</string>
    <string name="tqr2"><b>Round 2: Image Identification\n </b>1) Number of questions - 20\n 2) Time to solve - 10 min\n 3) Topic - General </string>
    <string name="tqr3"><b>Round 3: Rapid Fire\n </b>1) Time allotted - 90 sec per each\n 2) Maximum question attempt</string>
    <string name="tqr4"> <b>Round 4: Quizzy Buzzers\n </b>1) Questions will be announced verbally\n 2) First come first serve.</string>
    <string name="tqrules">1. No electronic devices are allowed.\n 2. Only single entry will be considered.\n 3. In each round elimination will be based on cut off value.\n 4. In case of tie there will be an another round.\n 5. Regarding the round conduction, instructions will be shared at execution time.\n 6. Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n 7. All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates".</string>
    <string name="csrules"> 1. Bring your college ID Card and Receipt on event day.\n 2. Two members are allowed in each team.\n 3. All Rounds are knockout.\n 4. First Round - 5 to 6 teams will play and winner of them will go for second round.\n 5. Winning will be based on first reaching to finish point or the team which is not eliminated from the game\n 6. All the winner of 1st Round will play for 2nd Round and so on.\n 7. The information will be provided to you at the time of event.\n 8. Maximum entry restrictions - 40 teams (on first come first basis)\n9. All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates".</string>
    <string name="bxcp"> • Number of participants per team: 7 Players and 1 Impact Player (optional) First 24 teams will be allowed for participation\n • Tournament will be of two days i.e. 7th &amp;; 8th Feb 2024\n • No re-entry and spot entry will be there\n • Team should include 5 Boys &amp; 2 Girls.</string>
    <string name="gr"><b>General Rules:\n </b>1) 7 players in one team &amp; 1 impact Player (optional)\n 2) First round 12 matches will be of 3 overs, Second round 6 matches will be of 3 overs and Third Round 3 matches will be of 4 overs\n 3) Semifinals 2 matches will be of 5 overs and Final will be of 6 overs\n 4) bowlers 1–1 over each and for next round only one bowler has 2 over and remaining 1–1 over\n 5) In Semifinals &amp; Finals, 2 bowlers has 2 overs and remaining 1–1 over\n 6) Some special rules will be conveyed at the time of Match\n 7) Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n 8) All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates "</string>

    <string name="battrules"><b>Batting Rules:\n </b>1) One Girl must open the inning with other batsman\n 2) Batsmen will be called out if he hits the ball over the boundaries (6 is out)\n 3) Each team should have their own bats (min 2). </string>

    <string name="ballrules"><b>Bowling Rules:\n  </b>1) Under arm bowling is compulsory\n 2) Ball should be pitched beyond the no ball line otherwise it will be called as no ball\n 3) Bowler has to ball within the given box without raising his leg. Any deviation from the above rules will be "NO BALL"\n 4) Usual NO BALL and WIDE BALL will be applicable\n5) Over throw runs will be counted.</string>
    <string name="md"><b>Mode of Dismissals :\n </b>1) Ball going over the boundaries, will be out if it doesn\t bounce inside the box\n 2) Caught out\n 3) Stumped out\n 4) Run out\n 5) No Argument will be entertained with the Umpire. Umpires decision will be the final\n 6) All rights reserved with The Organizers</string>
    <string name="cfr1"><b>Round 1: Technical Quiz\n </b>This round will consist of multiple choice questions based Test, test will be separate for both groups.</string>
    <string name="cfr2"><b>Round 2: Circuit Debugging\n </b>In this round, practical knowledge of Basic Electrical and Electronic Circuits of the participant Team will be tested. The Time limits will be mentioned on the day of event (details about It will be given on the spot). </string>
    <string name="cfr3"><b>Round 3: Circuit Geek\n </b>In this round, individual teams need to implement the Circuit according to the instructions</string>
    <string name="dytsj"><b>Judging :\n </b>• Creativity     • Flow of Design\n • Visual Impact     • Color Scheme\n • Quality of Application     • Effective conveying of theme message</string>
    <string name="dytsr">1. Participants shall bring their own materials like fabric or acrylic paints, glitters, brushes, mixing plate, pencil, pen, eraser.\n 2. White - T-shirts will be provided.\n 3. Use of any other materials or ready-made stickers is strictly NOT ALLOWED.\n 4. Participants shall not be allowed to use any photographs for reference.\n 5. Mobile phones or any other electronic devices shall not be allowed during the competition.\n 6. Any sort of tracing or copying is not allowed.\n 7. The art work should be relevant to the theme mentioned.\n 8. Duration of the competition will be of 2 hours.\n 9. Decision of the judges will be final and abiding.\n 10. After Jury you can take away your t-shirt.\n 11. Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day.\n 12. All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates ".</string>
    <string name="war"> • Submit projects and PPTs before 5th February. Students have to demonstrate their projects in proper format\n • Submission time should be strictly followed, no exceptions will be made\n • Judges will review entries, and results will be communicated on the venue\n •In 2nd round, only Shortlisted participants complete assigned tasks on-time within the specified timeframe\n •The final winner is chosen based on task completion and overall creativity\n • All the required material has to be brought by participant team themselves at event venue\n • Only internet facility will be made available by the organizing committee\n • Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n • All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates".</string>
    <string name="dthd">Description : Between treasure hunting and orienteering, "Digital Treasure Hunt" is a team building animation with a goal of building together."</string>
    <string name="dthr"><b>Rules &amp; Regulations \n </b>All participants must be seated at their designated competition areas for check time which is prior to assembly time. Only participants are allowed in the competition areas from this point forward\n The competition format for this challenge is:\n a) Qualifying rounds (best score taken and min time)\n b) Semifinals (1 round)\n c) Finals (1 round)\n • Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n • All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates".</string>
    <string name="thr1"><b>Round 1: Googler\n </b>Objective: Test participants ability to search and find relevant information on the internet quickly.\n\n Rules:\n • Participants are allowed to use the Google search engine or any specified warsh teel provided by the organizers\n • They will have a specific time limit to find and provide accurate answers or solutions.</string>
<string name="thr2"><b>Round 2: Puzzle\n </b>Objective: Assess participants problem-solving skills through various types of puzzles.\n\n Rules : \n• Participants will encounter different puzzles-riddles, brainteasers, logic puzzles, word puzzles or visual puzzles.\n • They must solve puzzle problems within a set time frame to progress to the next challenge.</string>
    <string name="thfr"><b>Final Round: Treasure Hunt\n</b> Objective: Participants will search for concealed clues or cheats scattered throughout a designated area or digital platform.\n\n <b>Rules:\n</b> • Clues may be hidden in various forms, such as coded messages, Images, or text, leading participants to the next stage of the round\n • Participants must locate and plece together these clues to progress towards the ultimate goal.</string>
    <string name="iplq"><b>1)Quiz Round \n </b>In this Quiz round the teams have been given a question paper of 30 questions which are to be solved into time limit of 30 minutes. The questions are MCQs which are related with the IPL or the events which are happened in IPL.\n For example, who is the highest wicket taker in last IPL ?\n After the quiz round only eight teams will be eligible for the next round the team will be selected as per the marin obtained in the quiz round.</string>
    <string name="iplar"><b>2) Auction Round:\n </b>After the quiz round the main round of auction will be held. The auction will as some as the IPL auction which is held every year before IPL. In this auction each team will be given a budget of 100 crore to buy the playen. The team have to buy the team of 11 players with 3 extra player that is total 14 players. The teams have to buy all the 14 players in the given budget. Suppose If any team will not be able to buy the player in the given budget then the team will be considered as disqualified team.\n\n For example,\n •M.S. Dhoni Bose value: 2 crore, Points: 95.\n • David Warner Base value 1.5 crore, Points: 88\n After the auction round the players which are purchased by the teams will be counted and the total of the points of all players will be done that is the total of the points of all 14 players will be done.\n The team with the highest value of points will win.</string>
    <string name="iplrules"><b>Rules And Regulations:\n </b>Maximum 3 participants per team\n Each team will be provided with some virtual money which can be considered as an individual team budget. Teams will have to bid for players and buy them\n At any moment of the game, teams crossing the stipulated budget stand to be disqualified\n Players are categorized, so by the end of the auction the structure of team should look like: 5 BATSMEN, 4 BOWLER, 1 ALL-ROUNDER , 1 LEGENDS (OF ANY Category), 1 WICKETKEEPER\n Teams not satisfying the mandatory structure in above will oho be disqualified\n Unsold players to be put up for auction or teams request or on demand\n The players list will be provided at the registration dels of the time of registration and the grades of player will be revealed only of the auction table\n Teams are expected to maintain discipline and only members should go the bid strictly\n Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n All the participants will be awarded with Participation Certificates"</string>
    <string name="iplwr"><b>Winner Rules\n</b>The teams with maximum number of points wins\n In case of the\n 1) The amount left for tied terms will be checked the cheoper team wall  the winning team\n 2) In case of some amount left the tide tears will have to nominate the bent botiman of the team and ODI statistics of the player will be checked head-to-head the team with the better player wins</string>
    <string name="pcr"> 1. Mini 1 and maxi 3 players can participate in this event.\n 2. Deck of cards and cardboard base will be provided.\n 3. Cutting, pasting and interlocking to playing cards is not allowed.\n 4. You will have to consume all cards compulsorily.\n 5. After completing, be quick to submit your model and record the height.\n 6. Team will have unlimited chances in the given time to construct and to record the height.\n 7. In case of multiple successful attempts, the Highest Recorded height will be considered for evaluation\n 8. In case of tie, Winner will be decided by giving extra time to construct\n 9. Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n 10. All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates ".</string>
    <string name="vinfo">• The players need not be physically present in the college premises for the tournament except the Finals\n • Teams will consist of 5 players (individually a "Participant" and together a "Team"), one of whom will be designated leader and will be the main point of contact the coordinators\n • All matches except the Grand Finals will be a Best-of-One. The Grand Finals will be played as a best-of-three\n • Players should be online 10 minutes prior to their scheduled matches\n • Organizers would not be held responsible for connectivity issues on the participants side\n• AFKs would not be entertained as an excuse for a rematch\n • Organizers reserve the right to accept or reject any entry without stating a reason there\n • Any abuse in chat is strictly prohibited. (If any one do so take a screenshot and share to the coordinators)\n• Although the Vanguard is sufficient enough to prevent any form of cheating but still if u experience anything fishy you can record the instance and send it to the coordinators and further action would be taken by the coordinators\n • If you dont get the chance to play then there would be a refund\n • Maps will be selected randomly\n • Waiting time is at most 10 minutes between games. GLHF y al!</string>
    <string name="nfsinfo">• Players should be physically present in the college premises on the event day. Using of any kind of cheat codes/ websites is prohibited\n • Players can use controllers to compete but it should be a plug-and-play type or else you have to play with the keyboard\n • Any player found cheating, misbehaving or misusing his/her chance will be disqualified\n • There will be adequate amount of customized cars, but even if you want your own car, you can customize it within 2 minutes prior to your race. Godspeed Racers!</string>
    <string name="bgmiinfo">1. It is a 4(+1) player team tournament. A 4 man-starter roster and up to 1 substitute\n 2. Emulators are not allowed in any game mode organized. The player will be disqualified if found using any kind of emulator\n 3. Any game modifying tools except GFX tool is not allowed\n 4. Players can play on android/ios tablets/phones only\n5. Only in-game voice chat should be used after the game is started till its completion\n 6. Any use of unfair means such as aimbot, trigger bot, ESP will be disqualified\n 7. Should a team/player fail to joint the room in time, their squad/they will be given O points for it\n 8. Waiting time is at most 10 minutes between games\n 9. Exiting a game without good reason will disqualify the team\n 10. The exploitation of bugs that hinders fair play will result in disqualification\n 11. For the tiebreaker of the points, total team/solo kills will be considered for breaking the tie\n12. For the further tiebreaker, number of chicken dinners will be considered\n 13. Organizers would not be held responsible for connectivity issues on the participants side\n 14. The entry fee would not be refunded under any circumstance\n 15. Organizers reserve the right to accept or reject any entry without stating a reason thereof\n 16. Participants are requested to remain ready at least 15 minutes prior to the start of any match. Late entries would not be allowed.</string>
    <string name="csinf">• Players should be physically present in the college premises on the event day.\n • Competition Method: 4v4 Players: 8 Total (4 on each team)\n • Rounds: 12 rounds for regulation play, 3 rounds of overtime play\n • Round Time: 1 minute 45 second cycle on a map\n • Max Rounds Format: 6 rounds as offense and 6 rounds as defense per team until the victory condition is met\n • Overtime: in the case of a 6–6 score at the end of Regulation Play, 3 overtime.\n • The start money for each team wil then be set at $10,000 per player for overtime.\n • Victory Conditions: The first team ot win 7 rounds in regulation or the team that wins the overtime period.\n • Buy Time: 30 seconds\n • Start Money: $800 for regulation Play, $10,000 for overtime Periods\n • Freeze Time: 01 seconds\n • C4 Timer: 55 seconds\n • Maps: De_dust2, De_inferno, De_piranesi, De_train GLHF.</string>
    <string name="cfinfo">• Participants Should Come On Time For The Test\n • All The Participants Should Have Valid Id-card of their respective institute with them\n • The hardware necessary for the final round will be provided by the organizer\n • The decision of judges &amp; the organizers will be final and binding to all.\n • Answer papers of 1 And 2 round will not be shown. All results are binding to all the Participants\n • In Case, any assistance is needed during the event, the teams should approach only the event coordinators / organizers\n • Maximum 2 members per team are allowed\n • Competition will Execute in Two Category.\n 1) Group A : (B.E. 1" Yr/ 11 and 12 Students/Diploma Students)\n2) Group B : (B.E.- Second/Third/Final/B.Sc./M.Sc. Students)\n • Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n• All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates".</string>
    <string name="rrinfo"><b>ROBO-RACE\n </b>ROBO- RACE Does racing run in your blood? Are you diehard fan of NFS most wanted, Formula 1 or any other racing game? If true, then we bring you the racing experience which will leave you thrilled.</string>
    <string name="rspeci"><b>Robot Specification:\n </b>1) The robot should be fit in the dimensions 25*25*25 cm (L*B*H)\n 2) Weight of robot should not exceed more than 3 kg.\n 3) Robot should be controlled by wired mechanism throughout the race (Wireless bots are not allowed).\n 4) Length of the wire must be sufficient to cover the arena\n 5) Wired robot will be provided by us or you can come with your robot with above specification</string>
    <string name="rrules"><b>Rules and Regulations:\n </b>1) A team can consist of min 1 and max 3 participants\n 2) Entry fees: 300/- per team\n 3) A team may consist of students from different colleges and each member should bring their college ID proof. POWER SUPPLY-Maximum allowed supply is 12 volt, 2 amp, will be provided by us. (External power supply is not allowed.) Maximum 3 hand touches is allowed\n4) Organizers may change the rules as per situation. Final decision will be taken by judges. Readymade toys cars and LEGO are not allowed.\n 5) If the participant causes any kind of physical damage to the opponent participants then, they will immediately disqualify. If the winner is not decided in the race then both the opponents will get disqualified.</string>
    <string name="rlj">ROBO Long Jump\n A trick is always to try collect the tries like trophies and you will never loose. You can\t always wait for the perfect time sometimes you must dare to jump.</string>
    <string name="rljr"><b>Rules and Regulations :\n </b>1) A team consist of min 1 and max 2 participants\n 2) Entry fees: 100/- per team\n3) A team may consist of students from different colleges and each member should bring their college ID proof\n 4) Robots will be provided by us. Two chances will be given\n 5) Organizers may change the rules as per situation per situation\n 6) Final decision will be taken by judges\n 7) Readymade toys cars and LEGO are not allowed</string>
    <string name="rljspeci"><b>Robot Specification :\n </b>1) The robot should be fit in the dimensions 25*25*25 cm (L*B*H)\n 2) Weight of robot should not exceed more than 3 kg.\n 3) Robot should be controlled by wired mechanism throughout the race (Wireless bots are not allowed).\n 4) Length of the wire must be sufficient to cover the arena\n 5) Wired robot will be provided by us or you can come with your robot with above specifications</string>
    <string name="rrspeci2"><b>Robot Specification :\n </b>1) Each robot should be manually controlled vehicle\n 2) The dimension of the robot should not exceed 33 cm (1)*25cm(b)*25 cm(h)\n 3) The robot should be remotely controlled and the connections (the wires, for instance) between the control unit and the robot should be slag at all times\n 4) Readymade toys and cars or LEGO are not allowed\n 5) Weight of the robot must not exceed 3kg (0.5 tolerance).</string>
    <string name="rrregu"><b>Rules and Regulations\n </b>1) Each team can consist of min 1 and max 3 participants\n 2) Entry fees: 300/- per team\n 3) There will be a maximum permitted time for different rounds ranging from 3 to 5 minutes. (1.5 min one half and 2 min maintenance break)\n 4) We will provide power point with 230 V 50 Hz on supply on extension cord and multipoint The potential difference between any two points must not exceed 12V at any point of the run\n 5) In final in case of a tie extra time of 1 min will be given which will be in two halfs of 0.5 min each round each match will be of 2 to 5 min in two halfs of 1 min each. Half time will be 2 min in which teams can repair their bots in case of any damage\n 6. The team will scores the first goal in the extra time, will be the winner.\n 7) If the winner is not decided after the extra time then event manager will decided how to separate the teams.</string>
    <string name="matr">1. There must be a minimum of 4 members in a team\n 2. Each group is allowed a single project based on "Real Life Applications"\n 3. Only a single-phase electric supply will be provided by the organizer\n 4. Project - related utilities must be carried by the group members\n 5. No students will be allowed to participate without a valid identity card.\n 6. Prizes will be awarded according to the assessment done by the judges\n7. The decision given by the judges in all matters will be final\n 8. Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n 9. All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates ".</string>
    <string name="sdr">1. Bridge it up on the screen\n 2. Only one member is allowed\n 3. Winning will be based on number of levels passed and minimum budget (weight) required to construct the bridge\n 4. Participants are not allowed to change the map or restart the game\n 5. Game settings cannot be changed during game time\n 6. Time duration : 30 minutes\n 7. Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n 8. All the participants will be awarded with Participation Certificates ".</string>
    <string name="spr">1. Bring your College ID–Card and receipt on Event Day\n 2. The teams will be given a maximum of 10 minutes (8+2) for presentation followed by a question and answer session\n 3. A paper should be in IEEE Format with an abstract should not exceed 300 words and paper size should be at most 5–10 pages.\n 4. In the IEEE format, the paper should only be in .docx or .pdf Format\n5. PowerPoint Presentation must be designed under the rules that is described in the TEMPLATE PPT.\n6. Templates for IEEE paper format and PPT are available on QR Code.\n7. While sending your paper please mention the authors name, contact umber and email ID in the Registration link \n8. Please bring 2 hard copies of the submitted paper on the day of the event \n9. All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates" \n10.Online mode is available for participants outside from Amravati University</string>
    <string name="ypr">• Each team shall comprise 2 members only\n • Certificate to all the participants\n • The quiz will comprise three rounds\n1) Qualifier Round\n2) Performance Round\n3) Final Round\n• Bring your college ID Cards and Receipt on event day\n• All the participants will be awarded with "Participation Certificates ".</string>
   <string name="rights">All Rights Reserved. Sipna COET, Amravati</string>
</resources>